

Tiago Rato Web Developer



ABOUT ME

I'm a determined, diligent person who discovered the love for programming. Having worked abroad for 10 years, I adapt very easily to multicultural environments.

I'm eager to learn, and I like to improve myself to become a better and valuable member of a team.



CONTACTS



+351 966 695 370



tiagorato13@hotmail.com



Vialonga, Portugal



https://www.linkedin.com/in/tiagorato



https://github.com/TiagoRato13



https://tiagorato.vercel.app/



SKILLS AND ABILITIES

HTML / CSS Node.js MongoDB

JavaScript

React SOL







Board Games





Scuba Diving **Paint**



PROJECTS

- Web CV / Portfolio
- Maria Luísa Psicologia
- <u>Precoce</u>
- Monster at the end of the tunnel
- Sebastião Alves



EDUCATION

FullStack Web Developer course January 2023 – March 2023 (Ironhack, Lisbon, Portugal)

Bootcamp program, over 500 hours focused on MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS) JavaScript, HTML and CSS. Create 3 full stack projects on each of the 3 modules presented using REST API's and CRUD operations

FullStack Web Developer course December 2021 – July 2022 (Lisbon, Portugal)

Learn basic to advanced level with multiple tasks to complete as well as a real final project including HTML/ CSS, PHP, SQL, Bootstrap and JavaScript (minimal), having finished with a final score of 19 out of 20.

Divemaster/Instructor Program January 2018 - May 2018 (Roctopus, Koh Tao, Thailand)

Bachelor of Cookery and food September 2007 - June 2010 production

(Estoril Higher Institute for Tourism and Hotel Studies, Estoril, Portugal)



EXPERIENCE

Contractor September 2020 - March 2023 (Habinterior, Lisbon, Portugal)

Operate and implement coordinated work programmes for smooth-running site operations. Maintain work in line with budget and schedule.

> **Dive Instructor** May 2018 - August 2020

Listen to client's concerns, provide additional information to ease anxieties and cultivate a relaxed atmosphere to enhance group enjoyment. Instil individuals and groups with confidence and motivation for productive sessions.

Chef

(Roctopus, Koh Tao, Thailand)

January 2011 - June 2017

(London, England)

Supervise all kitchen food preparation, in demanding, high-volume environment and deputise as head chef as needed to maintain team productivity and quality. Recruit and train kitchen staff to meet high expectations for performance and quality.